<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Luther Monson</title>
    <link>https://luth.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Luther Monson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 21:54:53 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luth.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recreating Proxmox Ve Xtermjs in Go</title>
      <link>https://luth.io/blog/2022/02/recreating-proxmox-ve-xtermjs-in-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 21:54:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luth.io/blog/2022/02/recreating-proxmox-ve-xtermjs-in-go/</guid>
      <description>Part of a hobby of mine is running a home lab and using on Proxmox VE to do the virtualization. Since I work in the space I&amp;rsquo;m slowly trying to build tooling around Proxmox that will let me use the home lab full time for work. Usually my work involves building Kubernetes management tooling, you can imagine waiting for public cloud APIs all day can take away hours of your day at cost to your employer for both your time and the compute resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Cue Example, Produce YAML Config from Go Types</title>
      <link>https://luth.io/blog/2022/01/practical-cue-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:57:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luth.io/blog/2022/01/practical-cue-example/</guid>
      <description>I recently had to spend some time to learn Cue and felt the examples/tutorials were a bit lacking and the paradigm shift to the entire language sort of messed with my head and some things Cue does were a bit foreign to me. To get started, note that the two places I spent all of my time to get this information came from their main docs and a community Cuetorials site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Blog Hosting Using Hugo &#43; Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://luth.io/blog/2022/01/free-personal-blog-hugo-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 11:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luth.io/blog/2022/01/free-personal-blog-hugo-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>Since I just rode this merry-go-round here is a quick overview of how you can achieve a professional looking personal blog with custom DNS with minimal effort at no cost and completely run out of a single Github Repository.
Prerequisites You&amp;rsquo;ll need to do your own homework on how to use Hugo and you should have a Github account and have a decent understanding of using git and getting changes committed and pushed to a repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://luth.io/blog/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 10:11:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luth.io/blog/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Getting a blog up and running to get some of the thoughts out of my head and into a markdown file. For reference on who I am please check out the about section and stay tuned for more content related to what it is I do everyday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
